<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homepage of Muhammad Afifurrahman on Muhammad Afifurrahman</title>
    <link>http://afifurra.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homepage of Muhammad Afifurrahman on Muhammad Afifurrahman</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://afifurra.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Research &amp; Education</title>
      <link>http://afifurra.github.io/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://afifurra.github.io/research/</guid>
      <description>Research Broadly speaking, I am interested in discrete mathematics, especially number theory, combinatorics, and finite fields. For my PhD, I am currently working on various problem related to integer equations of restricted height. During my bachelor and master studies, I did a total of two final projects over finite fields. However, I am open for learning other topics.
Publications Muhammad Afifurrahman. A uniform formula on the number of integer matrices with given determinant and height, submitted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Activities</title>
      <link>http://afifurra.github.io/activity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://afifurra.github.io/activity/</guid>
      <description>Other Mathematical Activities University of New South Wales Class Tutor for MATH1231 Mathematics 2A (2024-present) Class Tutor for MATH1081 Discrete Mathematics (2024-present) Drop-in Centre Tutor (2023-present) Exams Invigilator (2022-present) Exams &amp;amp; Assignments Marker (2022-present) Institut Teknologi Bandung Drop-in Centre Tutor (2019-2022) Exams Invigilator (2018-2022) Exams &amp;amp; Assignments Marker (2018-2022) Mathematical Olympiad Assistant Tutor, Indonesia International Mathematical Olympiad Training Camp (2017-present) Freelance mathematical olympiad tutor (2017-present) Reading Groups With Laurence Petrus Wijaya, I coordinate reading groups on mathematical papers in Bahasa Indonesia from 2023.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Other Works</title>
      <link>http://afifurra.github.io/other/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://afifurra.github.io/other/</guid>
      <description>Mettamatika Project Mettamatika Project comes from Spearhead Circle, a pop-culture collective based in Indonesia, with backbones from my friends in ITB. The main mission of Mettamatika is giving books that blend mathematical contents with pop cultures.
Being a part of the scripwriter team in Mettamatika Project (under nickname Furra), I have made a series of mathematical zines on statistical bias in Mettamatika vol 0.5 (2023), a calculus book for Mettamatika vol.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Links &amp; Musings</title>
      <link>http://afifurra.github.io/links/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://afifurra.github.io/links/</guid>
      <description>Yui Funami, YuruYuri. This was the frontpage picture for a long time, and when I changed the picture, my friend told me to let Yui stay here.
Other links Here are my English and Indonesian blogs (which are infrequently updated). During the pandemic, I often crash into some online mathematical research seminars from Research Seminars webpage. In fact, I first knew my doctoral advisor from the Number Theory Web Seminar that she organizes.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
