<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homepage of Muhammad Afifurrahman on Muhammad Afifurrahman</title>
    <link>http://afifurra.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homepage of Muhammad Afifurrahman on Muhammad Afifurrahman</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://afifurra.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>http://afifurra.github.io/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://afifurra.github.io/research/</guid>
      <description>Research Broadly speaking, I am quite interested in discrete mathematics, especially number theory, combinatorics, and finite fields. For my PhD, I am currently working on various problem related to equations of restricted height. During my bachelor and master studies, I did a total of two final projects on some objects over finite fields. However, I am open for learning other topics.
Publications Muhammad Afifurrahman, Alina Ostafe, and Igor E. Shparlinski. Statistics of ranks, determinants and characteristic polynomials of rational matrices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Education</title>
      <link>http://afifurra.github.io/education/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://afifurra.github.io/education/</guid>
      <description>Education PhD in Mathematics, University of New South Wales, Sydney, Australia (2022-present)
Current thesis topic: Arithmetic statistics of matrices (over sets of number theoretic interests). Advisor: Alina Ostafe &amp;amp; Igor Shparlinski MSc in Mathematics, Institut Teknologi Bandung, Bandung, Indonesia (2020-2021)
Thesis: Polynomial Parametrization for Some Classes of Maximum Sidon Sets over Finite Fields Advisor: Aleams Barra (also well-known for his YouTube channel) BSc in Mathematics, Institut Teknologi Bandung, Bandung, Indonesia (2016-2020)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Activities</title>
      <link>http://afifurra.github.io/activity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://afifurra.github.io/activity/</guid>
      <description>Selected Research Activities Participant, Research Experience in Mathematics, HSE University, Moscow, Russia (held virtually) (2021), supervised by Ilya V. Vyugin Research assistant under various research projects in ITB, with supervisors including: Aleams Barra, Intan Muchtadi-Alamsyah, Pritta Etriana Putri. Participant, AMSI Summer School 2023 at University of Melbourne (held hybrid) (2023). Here is my report as a grant recipient. Participant, International School on Algebraic Geometry and Algebraic Groups, Institute of Mathematics, VIAST (held virtually) (2021) Participant, Trimester Program on Harmonic Analysis and Analytic Number Theory, Hausdorff Institute of Mathematics (held virtually) (2021) Other Mathematical Activities University of New South Wales Casual Academic, responsible for inviligating and marking some first-year courses (2022-present) Drop-in Centre Tutor (2023-present) Institut Teknologi Bandung Grader for various courses, including Calculus, Introduction to Real Analysis, Introduction to Complex Analysis, Elementary Linear Algebra, and Introduction to (Proof-Based) Mathematics (2018-2022) Drop-in Centre Tutor (2019-2022) Mathematical Olympiad Assistant Tutor, Indonesia International Mathematical Olympiad Training Camp (2017-present) Freelance mathematical olympiad tutor (2017-present) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Achievements</title>
      <link>http://afifurra.github.io/award/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://afifurra.github.io/award/</guid>
      <description>Selected Awards Fast Track Program Awardee, Institut Teknologi Bandung (2020-2021) First Prize, International Mathematics Competition for University Students 2019. Gold Medal in Mathematics, Olimpiade Nasional Matematika &amp;amp; Ilmu Pengetahuan Alam 2019. Selected Scholarship and Grants UNSW Tuition Fee Scholarship + Research Stipend Scholarship Holder (2022-2026 (expected)) GTA 100 Scholarship Holder, Institut Teknologi Bandung (2020-2021) Selected Other Activities Scriptwriter in Metamatika Project at Spearhead Circle, a mathematical book project in Bahasa Indonesia that blends mathematics with popular culture (2023-present) Coordinator of Indonesian PhD student group at UNSW (2023-present) Contest Problem Proposer at Kontes Terbuka Olimpiade Matematika (2015-present, in Bahasa Indonesia) Guest Speaker at Podcast Bebas Linear (7 episodes, 2020-2023, in Bahasa Indonesia) Arranger of an Indonesian series of five talkshows on studying graduate mathematics abroad (2021-2022) Assistant for a graph theory-based board game under Aditya Purwa Santika at ITB (2020) Head of Media, Communication, and Information Division at Genshiken ITB (2018-2019) Head of Competition at MCF HIMATIKA ITB 2019 (2019) Co-founder of Pure Math Society at ITB &amp;ldquo;Purist MA LOL #makanyastrukal&amp;rdquo; (2018) Co-founder of Competitive Mathematics Society at ITB &amp;ldquo;Banceng Club&amp;rdquo; (2018) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Useful Links</title>
      <link>http://afifurra.github.io/links/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://afifurra.github.io/links/</guid>
      <description>Some links Here are my English and Indonesian blogs (infrequently updated).
During pandemic, I often crash into some online mathematical research seminars from Research Seminars webpage. In fact, I first knew my (current) doctoral advisor because she organizes the Number Theory Web Seminar that is posted there.
I like binge-reading mathematical blogs; in particular, Terence Tao&amp;rsquo;s and Igor Pak&amp;rsquo;s are worth reading.
I started to listen to some worldwide radio at Radio Garden</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quotes</title>
      <link>http://afifurra.github.io/quote/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://afifurra.github.io/quote/</guid>
      <description>Some throwaway quotes First off, I&amp;rsquo;m not interested in ordinary people. But, if any of you are aliens, time-travelers, or espers, please come see me. That is all! - Haruhi Suzumiya Abandoning your uniqueness is equivalent to dying. - Ryou Yamada Our everyday lives, may, in fact, be a series of miracles. - Mio Naganohara </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
